http://www.lincolntech.com/privacy

Skip to main content
Privacy PolicyEffective Date June 30, 2020 Our Commitment to PrivacyYour privacy is important to us at Lincoln Technical Institute, Lincoln College of Technology and Euphoria Institute (“Lincoln Tech”), and we are committed to safeguarding, preserving, and respecting the privacy rights of our customers and visitors. This online privacy statement (the “Statement” or “Notice”) describes how we collect, use, disclose, and the security of the personal information we gather about you through our website, https://www.lincolntech.edu (the “Website”) or otherwise. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.This Statement doesn’t apply to any other website maintained by other companies or organizations to which we link. Lincoln Tech is not responsible for the content or activities provided on those websites.You Consent to This StatementYou should read our complete & unabridged privacy policy. We recommend printing and retaining a copy of the complete policy for your future reference. By accessing, browsing, or otherwise using the Website, you confirm that you have read, understood, and agreed with this Statement. If you do not agree to this Statement, you may not use this Website.This Statement applies regardless of how the Website is accessed and will cover any technologies or devices by which Lincoln Tech makes the Website available to you.If you have any questions or concerns about our personal information policies or practices, you can contact us in the methods described below in the “How to Contact Us” section below. Take the Next Step
Complete this simple 3-step form to get started. Click NEXT to go to step 2.
Current:
Step 1
Step 2
Step 3
Email
Name First Name
Last Name
ProgramSelect A ProgramAestheticsAutomotive TechnologyCollision Repair and RefinishingComputer NetworkingCosmetologyCulinary ArtsDental AssistantDiesel TechnologyElectrical / ElectronicsHeavy EquipmentHVACInternational Baking and PastryMachining and ManufacturingMassage TherapyMedical AssistantMedical Assistant TechnologyMedical Coding and BillingMedical Office AssistantNail TechnologyPatient CarePractical NursingWelding Technology CampusSelect a CampusYou must select a program to see available campuses
